1 of 7

EXODUS MOVEMENT, INC.PRIVACY POLICY

Last Reviewed and Updated: February 25, 2021

Exodus Movement, Inc. and its subsidiary, Proper Trust AG (collectively, “Exodus,” “we,” “our,”and/or “us”), values the privacy of individuals who use our websites (including exodus.com (the“Website”)), applications, or services that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, our“Services”). This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) explains how we collect, use, anddisclose Personal Data from users of our Services. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy,“Personal Data” means information that relates to an identified or identifiable natural person.

By using our Services, you agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Data asdescribed in this Privacy Policy. Beyond this Privacy Policy, your use of our Services is alsosubject to our Terms of Service. If you are a California resident, our California Resident PrivacyNotice provides more information about your California privacy rights and explains how you canexercise those rights.

As the Exodus Wallet is a non-custodial crypto asset software wallet, we do not havecustomer accounts. We do not require you to provide your Personal Data to us to usethe Exodus Wallet. If you sign up for our newsletter or provide your Personal Data in acustomer service ticket, that information will be collected by us. However, certain thirdparty services may require you to provide them with Personal Data, in order to use theirservices within the Exodus Wallet.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We may collect limited Personal Data from or about you or your devices from various sources,as described below.

Information You Provide to Us. When you contact us or sign up for our newsletter, wecollect any Personal Data you provide to us, such as your name and email address. If youapply for a job with us, we will collect the Personal Data you provide to us through ourWebsite or via a third-party website in connection with your job application.

Information We Collect Automatically. We may automatically collect information about youand your devices when you use our Services. For example, when you visit our Website, wecollect your internet protocol (IP) address, web browser type, web browser language,operating system type, the website you visited before browsing to our website, the pages youview, the length of time you spend on a page, the dates and times of your visits, the hyperlinksyou click on, and other information about your use of our Website. When performing anexchange through our Services, we log information such as the wallet addresses and thetransaction IDs involved.

Cookies. We and our third-party partners may collect information using cookies, pixel tags, orsimilar technologies. Our third-party partners, such as analytics or advertising partners, mayuse these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and acrossdifferent services. Cookies are small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters.We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after

2 of 7

you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may beused by your browser on subsequent visits to our Services.

Our Website uses the following types of cookies for the purposes described below:

• Functional Cookies. We use functional cookies to recognize you when you returnto our Services.

• Analytics and Performance Cookies. We use analytics and performancecookies for website analytics purposes to operate, maintain, and improve theServices. The information gathered by these cookies is aggregated andanonymized and not identify any specific individual visitor. We use GoogleAnalytics to collect and process certain analytics data on our behalf. GoogleAnalytics uses its own cookies that help us understand how you engage with theServices and may also collect information about your use of other websites,apps, and online resources. The links below provide additional information andresources for Google Analytics:Google AnalyticsPrevent the Use of Google Analytics in Connection with your use of ourServices

• Advertising Cookies. We may allow third-party advertising partners to usecookies on the Services to collect information about your browsing activities overtime and across websites.

Further information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on yourdevice and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.

You can block cookies by setting your internet browser to block some or all of the cookies.However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) youmay not be able to access all or parts of our Services. You can change your browser settings toblock or notify you when you receive a cookie, delete cookies or browse our Services using yourbrowser’s anonymous usage setting. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen tolearn more about how to adjust or modify your browser settings. If you do not agree to our useof cookies or similar technologies which store information on your device, you should changeyour browser settings accordingly. You should understand that some features of our Servicesmay not function properly if you do not accept cookies or these technologies. Where required byapplicable law, you will be asked to consent to certain cookies and similar technologies beforewe use or install them on your computer or other device.

Information We Receive from Third Parties. We may receive Personal Data about you fromthird parties such as data or marketing partners and combine it with other Personal Data wehave about you.

3 of 7

HOW WE USE THE PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT

We use the Personal Data we collect for the following purposes:

• To provide, maintain, debug, improve, and enhance our Services.• To understand and analyze how you use our Services and develop newproducts, services, features, and functionality.• To communicate with you, provide you with updatesand other information relatingto our Services, provide information that you request, provide you with ournewsletter, respond to comments and questions, and otherwise provide customersupport.• For marketing purposes, such as developing and providing promotional andadvertising materials that may be useful, relevant, valuable, or otherwise ofinterest to you.• To personalize your experience on our Services such as identifying you as arepeat visitor.• To facilitate the connection of third-party services or applications.• To facilitate transactions such as an exchange.• To create de-identified and/or aggregated data to improve for our businesspurposes, including to improve our Services.• To process your job application.• To find and prevent fraud, detect security incidents, and respond to trust andsafety issues that may arise.• For compliance purposes, including enforcing our Terms of Service or other legalrights, or as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested byany judicial process or governmental agency.• For short-term, transient use.• To contract with service providers to perform services on our behalf, includingproviding customer service, processing job applications, verifying customerinformation, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analyticservices or providing similar services on behalf of the business or serviceprovider.• For other purposes for which we provide specific notice at the time the PersonalData is collected.

LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING EUROPEAN PERSONAL DATA

If you are located in the European Economic Area or the United Kingdom, we only process yourPersonal Data when we have a valid “legal basis”, including when:

● Consent. You have consented to the use of your Personal Data, for example, to send youmarketing communications or to use cookies.

● Contractual necessity. We need your Personal Data to provide you with the Services,for example, to respond to your inquiries.

● Compliance with a legal obligation. We have a legal obligation to use your PersonalData, for example, to comply with tax and accounting obligations.

4 of 7

● Legitimate interests. We or a third party have a legitimate interest in using your PersonalData. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Data for productdevelopment and internal analytics purposes, and otherwise to improve the safety,security, and performance of our Services. We only rely on our or a third party’s legitimateinterests to process your Personal Data when these interests are not overridden by yourrights and interests.

HOW WE SHARE THE PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT

We do not share or otherwise disclose Personal Data we collect from or about you exceptas described below or otherwise disclosed to you at the time of collection.

• Affiliates. We may share any information we receive with our affiliates for any ofthe purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

• Analytics Partners. We use analytics services such as Google Analytics tocollect and process certain analytics data. These services also may collectinformation about your use of other websites and online resources.

• As Required by Law and Similar Disclosures. We may access, preserve, anddisclose your Personal Data if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to:(i) comply with applicable laws; (ii) respond to law enforcement requests andlegal process, such as a court order or subpoena; or (iii) protect the rights,property, and safety of Exodus, our employees, agents, customers, and others,including to enforce our agreements, policies, and Terms of Service.

• Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers. We may transfer your Personal Data toservice providers, advisors, potential transactional partners, or other third partiesin connection with the consideration, negotiation, or completion of a corporatetransaction in which we are acquired by or merged with another company or wesell, liquidate, or transfer all or a portion of our assets.

• Vendors and Service Providers. We may share your information with vendorsand service providers retained in connection with the provision of our Services.

• Consent. We also may disclose your Personal Data with your consent.

INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS

Your information, including the Personal Data that you provide to us, may be transferred to, storedat and processed by us outside the country in which you reside, including, but not limited to theUnited States, where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level ofprotection as in other parts of the world. By providing any information, including Personal Data,on or to our Services, you consent to such transfer, storage, and processing. We may alsotransfer Personal Data from the European Economic Area or the United Kingdom to the UnitedStates, as needed, to perform the Services that you have requested from us. We will take stepsthat we believe to be reasonably necessary to treat your Personal Data securely and inaccordance with this Policy.

5 of 7

SECURITY

We use reasonable organizational, technical, and administrative measures to protectPersonal Data within our organization. However, as no electronic transmission or storageof Personal Data can be entirely secure, we can make no guarantees as to the security orprivacy of your Personal Data. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us isno longer secure, please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us via the“Contact Information” section below.

RETENTION

We will only retain your Personal Data as long reasonably required for us to provide therequested customer support and inquiry services. In the context of customer support, weretain information sufficient to connect subsequent requests from the same user in order toprovide efficient service, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (forexample for regulatory purposes). When determining the specific retention period, we takeinto account various criteria, such as the type of service provided to you, the nature andlength of our relationship with you, mandatory retention periods provided by law, and thestatute of limitations.

THIRD PARTIES

Our Services may contain links to other websites, products, or services that we do not own oroperate. We are not responsible for the privacy and advertising practices of these thirdparties. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to your activities on thesethird-party services or any Personal Data you disclose to these third parties. We encourageyou to read their privacy policies before providing any Personal Data to them.

DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS

Some Internet browsers may be configured to send "Do Not Track" signals to the onlineservices that you visit. There is no accepted standard on how to respond to Do Not Tracksignals, and we do not respond to such signals. To find out more about "Do Not Track,"please visit http://www.allaboutdnt.com

YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES

Opt-out. You may contact us anytime to opt-out of: (i) automated decision-making and/orprofiling; (ii) any new processing of your Personal Data that we may carry out beyond theoriginal purpose; (iii) any consent you previously provided to us regarding the processingof your Personal Data; or (iv) the transfer of your Personal Data outside the EEA. We willapply your preferences going forward and this will not affect the lawfulness of theprocessing before you withdrew your consent. Please note that your use of parts of ourWebsite may be ineffective upon opt-out.

Access. You may access the information we hold about you by contacting us viathe “Contact Information” section below.

Amend. You may update or correct any inaccuracies in your Personal Data by contacting usvia the “Contact Information” section below.

6 of 7

Restrict or Object. You may request us to restrict the processing of your Personal Data, orobject to our processing of your Personal Data via the “Contact Information” section below.

Move. Your Personal Data is portable – i.e. you to have the flexibility to move your data toother service providers as you wish.

Erasure. In certain situations, for example when the information we hold about you is nolonger relevant or is incorrect, you may request that we erase your data.

Exercising Your Rights. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us viathe “Contact Information” section below. In your request, please clearly describe: (i) whatPersonal Data is concerned and (ii) which of the above rights you would like to enforce.For your protection, we only process requests with respect to the Personal Data associatedwith the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need toverify your identity before processing your request. We will try to comply with your requestas soon as reasonably practicable and, in any event, within thirty (30) days of your request.Please note that there are exceptions and limitations to each of these rights, and that whileany changes you make will be reflected in active user databases instantly or within areasonable period of time, we may retain information for backups, archiving, prevention offraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwisereasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason for such retention.

Marketing Communications. You may unsubscribe from our promotional emails via thelink provided in the emails. Even if you opt out of receiving promotional messages from us,you will continue to receive administrative messages from us.

California Residents. If you are a California resident, you can review our CaliforniaResident Privacy Notice for information about your privacy rights and choices underCalifornia law.

COMPLAINTS

We are committed to resolve any complaints about our collection or use of your PersonalData. If you would like to make a complaint regarding this Privacy Policy or our practices inrelation to your Personal Data, please contact us as set forth below. We will reply to yourcomplaint as soon as we can and, in any event, within thirty (30) days. We hope to resolveany complaint brought to our attention; however if you feel that your complaint has not beenadequately resolved, you have the right to contact your local data protection supervisoryauthority.

CONTACT INFORMATION

We welcome your comments or questions regarding our privacy practices. If you havequestions about your privacy on the Services or this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at theaddress below.

Exodus Movement, Inc.15418 Weir Street, No. 333Omaha, NE 68137data@exodus.io

7 of 7

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on this page, and the revised versionwill be effective when it is posted. If we materially change the ways in which we use orshare Personal Data previously collected from you through our Services, we will attemptto notify you through our Services, by email, or other means
